We also carry out historic investments
on cultural heritage. We voted a cultural heritage
which has been extremely neglected in
decades. The Norwegian Property Agency has
received increased funding. We provide resources to
allows. Before Tidö there was no sperm
against bringing here relatives who were
only 18 years old, which means that
Sweden in practice saw through the fingers
on arranged child marriages. Today has
we such a barrier. Before Tide we were
probably most generous in Europe
the environmental code, which means that large
facilities can be erected without one
coherent assessment of environmental impact,
land use or landscape.
This has led to solar parks
economy that cripples welfare and
complications to everyday life for ours
compatriots. It imposes on our teachers and
doctor to document, register,
report and collaborate instead of
is absolutely not an impossibility that we
will have new legislation on this in
these questions that cater to many of
these motions before this one
term of office is over. I can't
Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
I will talk about public health. But health,
what is more important than health after all
coming around?
And whose responsibility is it? The question is not like that
heat waves just to be able to drink one
beer or glass of wine with the meal.
Systembolaget has a high trust so
let it remain. Give us one
alternative.
the state must be strong, efficient and
clear. It shouldn't be a colossus on
clay feet and then we have to trim the fat.
Eh, and we need to start shutting down
unnecessary authorities for the issue that we